Compass — a student success data environment.
Built by Syarifah Haninah.
All data is synthetic, calibrated to published sector benchmarks.
No real student records anywhere.
Executive view: 89.2% success rate — defined the Department of
Education way: EFTSL passed over EFTSL certified.
The persistent on-campus vs online gap is the story to watch
as online delivery grows.
Advisor triage: 4,096 students with active early alerts,
tiered P1–P4 to match caseload capacity.
No opaque risk scores — every alert carries plain-language
reasons an advisor can say out loud to the student.
Every alert has a lifecycle — raised, actioned, outcome — the
evidence chain the Support for Students Policy requires.
Row-level security, live: switching to the view of a single advisor...
...the list drops from 4,096 students to her 925, one campus group,
one caseload. Advisors see their students; managers see everything.
Back to the full view.
Needs-based Funding: $1.68M indicative funding for the 2026
equity cohort, broken down by category.
Every support case is tagged to the SEHEEF program logic at point
of entry — so the acquittal reporting generates itself.
Retention gaps are shown in demographic context —
never as raw league tables.
Is outreach working? A naive comparison is biased, because
advisors contact the hardest cases first.
Matched comparison recovers +4.9 points of persistence — validated
against a known effect injected into the synthetic data.
Data quality: every validation finding surfaced — a 100% catch
rate against the injected defect answer key.
Pipeline to dashboard, reproducible from code.
github.com/syarifahhaninah/compass-student-success